<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Dreamcast</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Dux.cdi</path>
		<name>Dux</name>
		<desc>DUX is a scrolling shooter in the vein of R-Type. When scientists searched for new materials to enhance their space ships, they discovered a new and powerful material they dubbed DUX. Since this type of material proved unstable, nobody except the player seemed brave enough to fly the space ship constructed from it. The player's job is to lead the ship through a series of horizontal levels against the Spiritual Spacers "to reach the obvious."

The player's ship has a standard laser shot that can be upgraded or changed for x-ray and bounce shots, which are very similar to the weapons in R-Type. The player also has a pod that protects them from enemy bullets and that can be launched as an offensive weapon in a move called "dash." Keeping the fire button pressed will launch a more powerful hyper shot.

To score points, the player can destroy chains of enemies in quick succession or soak up chains of bullets. Hyper Soaking makes the player invulnerable to bullets, but drains the Obvious Energy gauge if not enough bullets are soaked in or new energy orbs are picked up. The player wins the game if they manage to beat all the bosses at the end of each level. If they are hit by a bullet or collide with their surroundings, a life is lost. After all lives and continues are depleted, the game is over.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Dux.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Dux.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Dux.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hucast</developer>
		<publisher>Hucast</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marvel vs. Capcom 2 (USA).cdi</path>
		<name>Marvel Vs. Capcom 2 - New Age Of Heroes</name>
		<desc>Marvel vs. Capcom 2: New Age of Heroes is the sequel to the 2D fighting game Marvel vs. Capcom: Clash of Super Heroes. 

The game allows you to tag in all three players (instead of two, while the third is only used for special attacks, in the predecessor).

There are now up to 56 characters to use (most you have to unlock), including new characters like Jill Valentine from Resident Evil and Tron Bonn from Mega Man Legends.

Another new gameplay feature allows your team mates to come in during battle and give you a little health boost. This helps in lasting the distance in Survival mode, but they can also be hit by on coming attacks from the enemy.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Marvel vs. Capcom 2 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Marvel vs. Capcom 2 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Marvel vs. Capcom 2 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Stone (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Power Stone</name>
		<desc>The creators of Street Fighter add a new dimension to 3D fighting. In Power Stone, 2 fighters take to multi-level arenas with Power Stones and other weapons lying around for use.

Each game contains Power Stones. When you have enough stones (between three to five), your character transforms into an almost unbeatable warrior, with an all-new range of moves (although this does not last for long).</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Power Stone (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Power Stone (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Power Stone (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Stone 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Power Stone 2</name>
		<desc>The world's most revolutionary fighting game does it again! Power Stone 2 takes go-anywhere, grab-anything combat, and introduces awesome new innovations to the hit arcade fighting series. Now, up to four players wage insane battles in fully interactive, multi-level stages. Master over 120 different items used in battle - weapons, vehicles traps, power-upsand more! As if chaotic swashbuckling battles weren't enough, combine forces with other players to battle monstrous bosses to win the game!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Power Stone 2 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Power Stone 2 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Power Stone 2 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metropolis Street Racer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Metropolis Street Racer</name>
		<desc>Enter a new age of driving, a new form of thinking and feeling, and totally immerse yourself in the most advanced driving game ever created. Your 'Kudos' is the only path to success, since this is a unique test of skill, style and precision, which spans the streets of London, Tokyo and San Francisco. Be astounded by the realism, push your limits round 250+ different circuits, in hundreds of challenging events. Indulge up to 8 people in a unique multiplayer experience, and prepare yourself for the ultimate internet Kudos Challenge. From established racing game developers, Bizarre Creations, and featuring music from the renowned Richard Jacques, this game will change the way you think about driving forever.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Metropolis Street Racer (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Metropolis Street Racer (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Metropolis Street Racer (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bizarre Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving-Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat Gold (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat Gold</name>
		<desc>The first and only Mortal Kombat title to make onto the Dreamcast console, Mortal Kombat Gold offered players a carbon-copy of the arcade edition of Mortal Kombat 4, along with additional features and characters never before included in the arcade game.

Using the exact same engine found in Mortal Kombat 4, the game performs flawlessly on the Dreamcast platform, while also running at a higher resolution than its arcade counterpart.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mortal Kombat Gold (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mortal Kombat Gold (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mortal Kombat Gold (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aqua GT (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Aqua Gt</name>
		<desc>Aqua GT is powerboat racing game. It features three modes: Championship, Arcade and Two-player.

Championship mode is the main single player game, where you advance through the Bronze, Silver and Gold Championships. In the Arcade gameplay mode you have to beat the clock. In two-player split screen mode you go head to head against another player.

There are 5 boats to choose from, and you can unlock another 15 while progressing through the game. All boat vary in speed, acceleration and handling.

The tracks are set in canals of major cities, like London, Amsterdam and New York. Each track has a high or low tide, and you can race at day time or during the night time.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Aqua GT (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Aqua GT (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Aqua GT (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20001202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>East Point Software</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Confidential Mission (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Confidential Mission</name>
		<desc>Confidential Mission is a light-gun compatible shooting game most easily likened to Sega's Virtua Cop series.  You play as either Howard Gibson or Jean Clifford, both super-agents a la James Bond, and you are taken through scenarios shooting enemies and attempting to avoid civilian casualties.

The game is a home version of the coin operated arcade machine, and is playable by one or two players.  The game includes the popular features of the Virtua Cop series "Justice Shot" (in which you shoot an enemy's gun or gun arm instead of killing them) and the "Combo Shot" in which you can hit an enemy with up to three shots before they expire.  The home version does include some mini-games and training modes that were not in the arcade version of the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Confidential Mission (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Confidential Mission (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Confidential Mission (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010514T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cosmic Smash (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Cosmic Smash</name>
		<desc>Cosmic Smash for Dreamcast is a port of the Sega Rosso arcade game. It is a futuristic sports game, a mix of squash and Breakout.

The player controls a semi-transparent human male in third-person view. The goal is to clear each level from a set of different blocks at the far end of the room within a given time limit. Additional time is given at the start of the next level depending on how well the player did. To clear the room, the player has to hit a ball with a racket at the correct angle. The ball bounces back from the blocks and walls. The blocks have different properties, for example, some have to be hit multiple times before they disappear, while others move around thus making them harder to hit.

Besides the regular shot, the player can also perform a trick shot, which in combination with other moves gives extra points when successfully executed. At the end of each level, a map with branching paths is displayed, enabling the player to take different routes towards the end of the game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Cosmic Smash (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Cosmic Smash (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Cosmic Smash (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Death Crimson OX (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Death Crimson OX</name>
		<desc>On July 29, 2010, the city of Saronica comes under attack by an army of monsters called the SMO as they lay siege to the city, capturing it and ruling the populace under an iron fist.  During this, The Resistance is formed in an attempt to stop the SMO, lead by a woman by the name of Lily who is kidnapped when she attempts to help a man by the name of Kou.  After she is captured, it is learned the man has come into possession of two ancient pistols by the name of "Crimson" that can destroy the monsters and their vicious leader.  Kou sets out with Lily's daughter, Yuri, to bring her back and stop the evil forces within the city.

Death Crimson is a light-gun game similar in style to House of the Dead where the player shoots at enemies that pop up on screen and save innocents from the monsters.  The player can also power-up the "Crimson" pistols by shooting death flowers that will turn their firepower into machine guns to decimate hordes of enemies.  There is also a health meter that will increase in size by successfully shooting enemies, gaining experience points.   Once enough points are obtained, the health bar will increase, however missing enemies or shooting civilians will take away points.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Death Crimson OX (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Death Crimson OX (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Death Crimson OX (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ecole</developer>
		<publisher>Ecole</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Expendable (USA).cdi</path>
		<name>Expendable</name>
		<desc>In 2463 a race of vicious aliens has invaded human planets, wiping out the population of Novocastria first. Only the Millennium Soldier can lead the human fightback. 

In this sci-fi action game, reflex shooting dominates over planning or tactical play. Expect non-stop action from fighting and relentlessly killing off tons of bad guys across more than 20 levels of 3rd person 3D action, taking place inside and outside. Powering up your weaponry is crucial - there are 18 different ones to collect, from pulse cannons to particle accelerators and rockets to missiles. Two player cooperative and deathmatch modes are provided.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Expendable (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Expendable (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Expendable (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rage Software</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fighting Vipers 2 (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Fighting Vipers 2</name>
		<desc>This game is a sequel to Fighting Vipers, a 3D fighting game that allows you to face adolescents and adults that comes from different "urban tribes", but also, in that second version you can choose or beat another time the most charismatic characters of FV1 and some unedited characters never seen again (either in FV2 arcade, version appeared in 1998 on Model 3 arcade board).

FV2, as in FV, has the incentive to destroy the fight arena walls with the last combat impact, also, you can destroy again the armor of your opponent, that as a newness in 1998's FV2, includes the "Super KO System", in which, if you break the armor of your opponent and immediately, you make a Super Combo that leaves him "confused", you will win without dispute a second round.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fighting Vipers 2 (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fighting Vipers 2 (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fighting Vipers 2 (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Volgarr the Viking.cdi</path>
		<name>+☆Volgarr the Viking</name>
		<desc>Do you have what it takes to be the greatest Viking Barbarian Lord in the world? Return to the Golden Age of arcade gaming with all-new hardcore action experience that pulls no punches. Playing as Volgarr the Viking, use your sword and spear to slaughter your foes in bloody combat. Battle Gigantic bosses in every world and find secrets that lead to unknown paths. Holding onto Volgarr's gear is key; his very life depends on it.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Volgarr the Viking.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Volgarr the Viking.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Volgarr the Viking.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20150424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./fotns.zip</path>
		<name>+☆FIST OF THE NORTH STAR</name>
		<desc>This was an arcade game released in 2000 by Konami (also known as Punch Mania: Hokuto no Ken)</desc>
		<image>./mixart/fotns.png</image>
		<video>./snap/fotns.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/fotns.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20050101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fighter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GunLord (2012)(NGDEV.TEAM).cdi</path>
		<name>+☆Gunlord</name>
		<desc>Gunlord is a Eurostyle Platformer with emphasis on exploring huge worlds and blasting off enemies. This game features 8 stages of exciting 2D game play with over 45 unique enemy types. Blast yourself through giant landscapes, explore caverns and reveal all secrets!!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/GunLord (2012)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</image>
		<video>./snap/GunLord (2012)(NGDEV.TEAM).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/GunLord (2012)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20120621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Plateform / Fighter Scrolling-Platform</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Last Hope - Pink Bullets (2011)(NGDEV.TEAM).cdi</path>
		<name>+☆Last Hope - Pink Bullets</name>
		<desc>The evil empire is rushing at light-speed across the galaxies, heading towards Mother Earth. Barely 24 hours ago, they penetrated the last defence line of our galaxy, the Arsion Laser Belt. Millions of innocent people perished in outer space colonies. 70% of our fleet was destroyed during first contact. Our intelligence has now extrapolated their arrival within six days. Conventional weapons cannot stop them. Our last hope is in your hands: The Z-42 Warpstar. Warp into their territories and destroy their leader before they reach Earth.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Last Hope - Pink Bullets (2011)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Last Hope - Pink Bullets (2011)(NGDEV.TEAM).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Last Hope - Pink Bullets (2011)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20090904T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal-Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Neo XYX (2014)(NGDEV.TEAM).cdi</path>
		<name>+☆Neo Xyx</name>
		<desc>NEO XYX is early 90is style maniac shooting game. Fast and intense.nnnnGame Features:nnnn    6 stages with varied and colorful settingsnn    6 endbossesnn    5 midbossesnn    16-bit hand-drawn graphics (dot graphics)nn    Switchable between vertical (TATE) and horizontal controls (YOKO)nn    The HUD/score/lives/bombs etc. switch between TATE and YOKO too.nn    Maniac shooting gamnn    Professional printed CD</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Neo XYX (2014)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Neo XYX (2014)(NGDEV.TEAM).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Neo XYX (2014)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20140217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Grind Radio (USA).cdi</path>
		<name>Jet Grind Radio</name>
		<desc>Jet Set Radio is a video game developed by Smilebit and published by Sega on June 29, 2000. Jet Set Radio was developed for the Dreamcast, although a 2D version of the game was later released for Game Boy Advance and was developed by Vicarious Visions, and published by THQ. Its sequel, Jet Set Radio Future was released 2 years later for the Xbox after SEGA became a software-based company. The game is known for spearheading the use of cel-shaded graphics in video games.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Jet Grind Radio (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Jet Grind Radio (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Jet Grind Radio (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Smilebit</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega GT (USA).cdi</path>
		<name>Sega GT</name>
		<desc>With a nod towards GT2, Sega tosses in their entry in the race-career-category, meaning that this game is all about racing. Racing to win competitions, cars, money and other prizes (such as licenses for bigger cars), buying new cars to race in, upgrading cars to race in and gaining licenses to race with.

It features realistic controls, graphic and physics, and spans over career, multiplayer or arcade modes, and hundreds of cars to boot.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sega GT (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sega GT (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sega GT (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow Man (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Shadow Man</name>
		<desc>You're the Shadow Man, a person who can switch between the world of the dead and of the living. In Shadow Man your mission is to prevent 5 serial killers from bringing the total armageddon. In the world of the living, you're mortal and have conventional weapons. When you die, you are transported to the world of the dead and you become Shadow Man once again. Which means you're not really mortal. In the world of the dead you can't use normal weapons, your gun shoots ghosts which kill the zombies and the other ugly creatures which live there. You also have different voodoo powers and weapons. And you're carrying a large inventory around.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Shadow Man (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Shadow Man (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Shadow Man (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure-Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Calibur (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Soul Calibur</name>
		<desc>A fighting game to end all fighting games.  A sequel to Soul Blade, Soul Calibur takes place in a time inspired by a mixture of 16th-century ancient China and oriental medieval fantasies and legends.  

All characters have weapons and distinct fighting styles with over 100 individual moves per character.  In addition to high, mid, and low attacks, characters can hold/throw, block, and perform special attacks -- one or more of which is deemed "un-blockable" and must be avoided by ducking, jumping, or rotating around your attacker. 

In addition to several locales in which to fight and alternate models/costumes per character, the Dreamcast conversion of Soul Calibur contains many additional features over the arcade coin-op, including hidden characters and locales, a campaign mode, and tournament mode.  There is also a "museum" where you can view character profiles and view motion-captured martial arts demonstrations.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Soul Calibur (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Soul Calibur (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Soul Calibur (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fight</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Episode I Racer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Star Wars - Episode I - Racer</name>
		<desc>Based upon the Pod Racing scenes of Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace, your mission as young Anakin Skywalker or as one of a collection of strange characters from around the Galaxy is to compete, survive and win in the high speed challenge of Pod Racing.

Each character has a unique Pod that can be upgraded with the credits you win after each race. Finish first to gain the most prestige and compete in greater and more challenging tracks, including the now famous race along the sand dunes of Tatooine that determined the destiny of many lives.
</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Star Wars - Episode I Racer (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Star Wars - Episode I Racer (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Wars - Episode I Racer (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000404T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sturmwind.cdi</path>
		<name>Sturmwind</name>
		<desc>You found the way in now find the way out! Survive 16 levels and even more big grumpy boss enemies</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Sturmwind.png</image>
		<video>./snap/Sturmwind.mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Sturmwind.png</marquee>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20130424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Redspotgames</developer>
		<publisher>Redspotgames</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Magnetic Neo (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Super Magnetic Neo</name>
		<desc>In Super Magnetic Neo, a gang lead by evil, foul-mouthed baby Pinki has taken over Pao Pao Park.  The professor must stop her, so her sends Super Magnetic Neo, a little boy robot with a powerful electromagnet on his head.

The game has some resemblance to the Crash Bandicoot series in that some levels have you running toward the camera, have a side-view, or have you riding an animal.  It contains some running, jumping and switch-flipping much like any 3D platformer.  However, it does have a unique magnetism aspect.  Positive and Negative charges are represented by red and blue.  Neo's head can act as a positive or negative pole.  This is called his magnogimmick.  Using the principle of opposites charges attract and similar charges repel, Neo can pull himself toward platforms, then launch off them, or navigate many related environmental puzzles such as pulling himself into teleporters or swinging on magnetic pendulums.  Enemies also come in red and blue and can pulled pulled in to be captured or pushed away to be avoided accordingly.

You must use all these skills to make it through all four sections of Pao Pao Park and defeat Pinki.

There is also a challenge mode, with a series of short stages to pass all based around proper use of the magnogimmick.  It's something like the VR missions in the Metal Gear series.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Magnetic Neo (Europe).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Magnetic Neo (Europe).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Magnetic Neo (Europe).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crave Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris 4D (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Tetris 4D</name>
		<desc>Tetris 4D is a fairly standard Tetris game that was released in Japan shortly after the Dreamcast launched.

The game features two modes, Classic and Battle. Classic mode offers a normal solitaire Tetris game: rotate and fit falling blocks to complete lines. Five difficulty settings are available, which change the speed and piece preview settings.

The sound and graphics generally follow a modern urban/industrial theme, with five techno music choices, including a variation of the classic Tetris "Karinka". The 3D backgrounds are basic but shift viewpoint as you advance in levels.

The Battle mode offers two to four player multiplayer. One player starts off flagged, and blocks push up from the bottom as other players make lines. Once he makes enough lines himself the flag moves to another player. Difficulty is set independently allowing for handicaps.

Unfortunately, you can't play the battle mode against the computer. There's also no VMU support for saving high scores, a rather critical omission for this type of game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Tetris 4D (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Tetris 4D (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Tetris 4D (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Bullet-Proof Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Time Stalkers (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Time Stalkers</name>
		<desc>You are walking down a lonely country road, thinking about a girl when suddenly you are attacked. You fend him off with your sword, he runs.  You are Sword the mighty warrior, so you give chase and find yourself, eventually, in a land that is a quiltwork of different cultures and styles. 

You have been selected to save this world.  As you complete each challenge,  another land is added to the core world.  As you progress,  you gain allies and eventually have up to 6 characters to use for your quests.  You can capture and build up monsters to assist you.  You can purchase and create weapons to defeat your foes.  You can even use credits gained in the VMU games to help in the development of your characters and dungeons.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Time Stalkers (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Time Stalkers (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Time Stalkers (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Climax</publisher>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rainbow Cotton (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Rainbow Cotton</name>
		<desc>Another shooter in the Cotton saga. Trouble brews in the homeland of Cotton's long time friend Silk, as the evil demon Suede steals the legendary Willow candy from the queen's castle. Seeing as how no one can face Suede and his forces Silk drafts Cotton in order to restore peace to her land, but she may have forgotten that Cotton is a big fan of Willow candies herself...

Gameplay-wise Rainbow Cotton actually follows in the steps of Panorama Cotton as the gameplay switches from a 2D perspective to a 3rd person one. The gameplay itself however is reminiscent of games like Panzer Dragoon, in which you don't control Cotton as she flies, but instead where she aims with her magic spells. You can shoot down enemies as well as open chests, doors and other bonus locations for power-ups and spells, which advance Cotton's abilities in an rpg-lite fashion and increase your arsenal with different magical powers.

Taking advantage of the technological advances, the game uses for the first time polygonal graphics and to complement the action the game features 2D animated cutscenes between levels.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Rainbow Cotton (Japan).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Rainbow Cotton (Japan).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Rainbow Cotton (Japan).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Success Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fast Striker (2010)(NGDEV.TEAM).cdi</path>
		<name>+☆Fast Striker</name>
		<desc>Fast Striker is an arcade-style vertical shooter with a science fiction setting. While the game is essentially 2D, the backgrounds consists of pre-rendered 3D graphics. This game features six stages with over 40 enemy types.    You can choose between 3 game modes (Novice, Original and Maniac) with different scoring systems. The modes differ, for example, in the set of available techniques. In comparison to the Novice mode, the Original mode features a shield to protect the ship, which can be activated for a short time, and holding the down the spread fire button will also shoot rockets after a few moments. Furthermore, the enemies are colored differently in Novice mode to make them more visible, and you collect golden stars as part of the scoring system. The Maniac mode adds some new ways to get higher scores. For example, the distance between your ship and an enemy influences the score: you get a larger bonus the nearer you are to the enemy ship when you destroy it. Destroying many enemies in short time will also increase the number of awarded points. Last, you can activate a "Grind Mode" by focusing your ship's laser beam on a huge enemy. The beam will turn green after a while and then all destroyed enemies will give a higher score.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Fast Striker (2010)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Fast Striker (2010)(NGDEV.TEAM).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Fast Striker (2010)(NGDEV.TEAM).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
		<favorite>true</favorite>
	</game>
</gameList>