<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Nintendo 64</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game id="71667" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Batman Beyond - Return of the Joker (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Batman Beyond : Return of the Joker</name>
		<desc>Based off the movie, Batman Beyond puts the player on the streets of Gotham (Beyond) to take out the ever-grinning Joker, but before that an obvious long line of his evil minions - some of which are genetically engineered.

Scroll around, punch, kick, play with bat-weapons, and avoid being on the receiving end of those attacks. There are multiple 'bat suits' that you can choose from, each with their own special abilities and purposes.

Mostly a 3-D beat-the-living-sunshine-out-of-whatever-moves type.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20001213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Action-Beat'em Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Batman Beyond - Return of the Joker (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Batman Beyond - Return of the Joker (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Batman Beyond - Return of the Joker (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="5428" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Legacy of Darkness</name>
		<desc>Set in the year 1844, the game stars the man-beast Cornell in his quest to prevent his adoptive sister, Ada, from being used as a sacrifice to resurrect Dracula. The game opens as Cornell arrives at his village, which has been burned to the ground by Dracula's minions. He finds Ada's pendant in a doorway and follows her scent to Dracula's castle.

During the course of the game, Cornell comes upon a grand estate owned by the Oldrey family: J.A. Oldrey, the master of the Villa, Mary, his wife, and Henry, their son. Gilles de Rais and Actrise have turned Oldrey Senior into a vampire. At Mary's request, Cornell guides Henry to safety. Later in life, Henry returns to Castlevania to save kidnapped children.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Adventure-Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="5567" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Chopper Attack (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Chopper Attack</name>
		<desc>In Chopper Attack, you take a chopper and.. well.. attack! You get to choose between eight different attack choppers, each having its own strengths and weaknesses. 

After the briefing from your XO, you are set to destroy something - tanks, other helicopters, planes, radars, buildings etc. While the mission only requires you to do something specific, destroying everything gives you bonuses and money, which you can then use to buy more heavy-duty missiles between the missions.

If you look at the screenshots, you might think that Chopper Attack is a helicopter simulation. It's not. Your elevation is fixed. There are no physics. You have boss fights with GIANT choppers. The game is pure 3D action, plain and simple.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19980617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SETA Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Midway - Seta</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving-Action-Shooter-Shooter / 3rd person</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Chopper Attack (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Chopper Attack (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Chopper Attack (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="5404" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Donkey Kong 64 (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 64</name>
		<desc>K. Rool has kidnapped the Kongs! Can Donkey Kong rescue his friends, reclaim the Golden Bananas and save his homeland from certain doom? Take out some Kremlings with Chunky's Pineapple Launcher or Lanky's Trombone. Float through the air using Tiny's Ponytail Twirl. Even rocket to the sky with Diddy's Jetbarrel!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure-Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Donkey Kong 64 (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Donkey Kong 64 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Donkey Kong 64 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="5456" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Duke Nukem - Zero Hour (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem : Zero Hour</name>
		<desc>He's all that stands between us and a Time-Spanning Alien invasion. He's Duke Nukem. Gaming's Greatest Action Hero. And this is his finest hour! Zero Hour! Awesome new enemies! Hilarious gags and one-liners! Same blood and guts attitude! Over 30 gut-wrenching levels set in four action-packed time eras! Incredible Teamplay and Deathmatch modes for up to 4 players! Over 20 all-new weapons of high-octane annihilation.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19990801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / 1st person-Action-Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Duke Nukem - Zero Hour (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Duke Nukem - Zero Hour (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Duke Nukem - Zero Hour (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="5489" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Harvest Moon 64 (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon 64</name>
		<desc>In Harvest Moon 64, your objective is to restore a run-down farm that you've inherited from your grandfather, who has died recently.  In the village many people help you out on your long journey.  During this time you can attend festivals, race in horse races, farm, tend to your livestock, add to your house, get married, or maybe even have a child.  There are 5 beautiful women to be chosen from, each having their own jobs and personalities.  At the end the player's parents come by and rate them after 2 and a half years of performance.  The option then exists either to keep going or stop there.  The real question is if you're up for the challenge.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pack-In</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Harvest Moon 64 (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Harvest Moon 64 (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Harvest Moon 64 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="5438" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Kirby 64 : The Crystal Shards</name>
		<desc>Dart past enemies, soar the skies and swim the depths of the ocean as Kirby takes on Dark Matter in an all-new adventure. Inhale, exhale and swallow your enemies, then copy and combine their abilities and use them as your own! Team up with familiar friends and foes - like Waddle Dee and King Dedede - as you travel through dreamy worlds in search of the lost Crystal Shards.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory - Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="5510" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Mace - The Dark Age (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Mace : The Dark Age</name>
		<desc>Live by the sword. Kill for the mace! Forged in the fires of the Dark Ages, Mace is the hottest 3D fighting game ever! Each medieval character wields a weapon unique to their land of origin. Their only desire - inflict serious pain! Sixteen player-selectable characters, two amazing bosses and six hidden characters. Tons of tasty combos and reversals with simple four-button controls. Become immersed in battle with complete 3D character movement. Behold the interactive multi-level arenas, but beware of the deadly boundaries!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19971001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./mixart/Mace - The Dark Age (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mace - The Dark Age (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Mace - The Dark Age (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="5400" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Paper Mario (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Paper Mario</name>
		<desc>Mario pals around in an all-new action adventure! Mario's back in his first adventure since Super Mario 64, and this time, Bowser's bent on preventing a storybook ending. When Princess Peach is kidnapped, Mario plots to rescue the seven Star Spirits and rid the Mushroom Kingdom of Koopa's cruel cohorts. As he travels from the tropical jungles of Lavalava Island to the frosty heights of Shiver Mountain, he'll meet up with seven all-new companions... and he'll need help from each one or there'll be no happily ever after.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Intelligent Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./mixart/Paper Mario (USA).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Paper Mario (USA).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Paper Mario (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game id="5416" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
		<path>./Star Fox 64 (USA) (Rev A).n64</path>
		<name>Star Fox 64</name>
		<desc>The Lylat system has been invaded! Join Fox McCloud and his Star Fox team as they fight to save the galaxy from the clutches of the evil Andross. Travel to many different 3-D worlds. Battle the enemy in the air and on the ground and listen in as Fox McCloud interacts with a cast of characters.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./mixart/Star Fox 64 (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
		<marquee>./wheel/Star Fox 64 (USA) (Rev A).png</marquee>
		<video>./snap/Star Fox 64 (USA) (Rev A).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Snap (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Pokémon Snap</name>
		<desc>Professor Oak needs your help!

The Professor has asked you to capture the Wild Pokémon of Pokémon Island… on film!  Tour the island in your ZERO-ONE vehicle and snap pictures of Pokémon in their natural habitat.  Wild Pokémon are often camera-shy, so you’ll have to use special items to bring them out in the open.  Only the best shots will do for the Professor’s Pokémon Report, so sharpen your photography skills and get ready to SNAP!

* The first-ever N64 game to feature the world-famous Pokémon--fully rendered in 3-D!
* Explore the many environments of Pokémon Island, like the sunny beach, the mysterious caves, and even a red-hot volcano!
* Many different types of Pokémon inhabit the island.  See how many you can catch on film!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Pokemon Snap (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Pokemon Snap (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Pokemon Snap (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory | Pax Softnica</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Life Simulation</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quest 64 (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Quest 64</name>
		<desc>You play the young hero Brian in his quest to save the land of Celtland.  Brian's father, Lord Bartholomy, has mysteriously disappeared.  The Eletale Book has also been stolen, which preserves harmony in Celtland.  Brian must find his father and bring back the Eletale Book.

Quest 64 is the very first RPG made for the Nintendo 64.  It features colorful graphics in a fully 3D world.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Quest 64 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Quest 64 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Quest 64 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineer</developer>
		<publisher>Imagineer</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Role playing games</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Smash Bros. (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros.</name>
		<desc>Super Smash Brothers takes familiar Nintendo characters such as Mario, Kirby and Donkey Kong, and gets them to fight to the death. There are 8 fully-interactive landscapes, with one for each character, with noticeable links to their games. Controls are analogue-based, with different moves executed depending on the direction and how firmly the stick is pressed. Items like baseball bats, Bob-ombs, and healing items drop into the arenas at random, aiding any nearby characters than can make use of them. The game uses a fixed viewpoint which scrolls, although characters are rendered in 3D.

The one-player mode has 14 stages to work through. Up to 4 human players can do battle at once, with team play as well as all-against-all action. Hidden characters are thrown in for good measure, as are bonus rounds, and a battle to the end with a giant hand (you read right).

Playable characters include:

1. Captain Falcoln* (F-Zero series)
Donkey Kong (Donkey Kong games)
Fox (Star Fox series)
Kirby (Kirby games)
Jigglypuff* (Pokémon universe)
Link (Legend of Zelda series)
Luigi* (Mario games)
Mario (Mario games)
Ness* (Mother/EarthBound series)
Pikachu (Pokémon universe)
Samus (Metroid series)
Yoshi (Mario games)

* denotes any characters that need to be unlocked under special conditions first.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Smash Bros. (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Smash Bros. (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Smash Bros. (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory - Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fight-Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).n64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Majora's Mask</name>
		<desc>Thrown into a parallel world by the mischievous actions of a possessed Skull Kid, Link finds a land in grave danger. The dark power of a relic called Majora's Mask has wreaked havoc on the citizens of Termina, but their most urgent problem is a suicidal moon crashing toward the world. Link has only 72 hours to find a way to stop its descent.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Action / Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms Armageddon (USA) (En,Fr,Es).n64</path>
		<name>Worms Armageddon</name>
		<desc>The final sequel (at least using the present engine) to the strategy game Worms, Worms Armageddon expands on Worms 2 by improving quite a few facets of gameplay and including play over the Internet through Team 17's WORMNET. 

For those who've never played Worms, it's at heart similar to the old game Artillery, which you control an artillery piece. In essence, you give it a shot angle and shot power, and try to hit your enemy, despite wind effects and the enemy firing back at you. Worms puts you in command of a team of Worms, but not only can you move around the landscape, you can use many types of weapons to try to dispatch the enemy, from bazookas to mini-guns to exploding sheep. 

Everything is presented in a humorous cartoonish style, from the landscapes to the worms themselves and their cries of triumph or despair, depending on how you do.

Armageddon uses an enhanced version of the Worms 2 engine, and while an improvement over Worms 2, it's not a huge change.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Worms Armageddon (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Worms Armageddon (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Worms Armageddon (USA) (En,Fr,Es).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames - Team17</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WWF No Mercy (USA) (Rev A).n64</path>
		<name>WWF No Mercy</name>
		<desc>The last wrestling title made by the team of THQ and AKI allows players to compete for 7 different WWF Titles with each belt getting its own unique story. Stories can be replayed, allowing players to defend their title in a storyline. Upon successful completion of a story mode, players will unlock the title they were competing for in Exhibition mode where titles can be won and defended as the players see fit.

A maximum of 4 players can compete in a range of modes, including caged and ladder contests and pay per view events. You can also create your own event and compete for WWF titles unlocked in Championship mode. Certain matches will take you outside the ring to 4 different backstage locations.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/WWF No Mercy (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
		<video>./snap/WWF No Mercy (USA) (Rev A).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/WWF No Mercy (USA) (Rev A).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AKI Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Sports-Sports / Wrestling</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Story (USA) (En,Ja).n64</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Story</name>
		<desc>Loosely based on the Super NES classic Yoshi's Island, Yoshi's Story follows the adventures of six Yoshis as they search through sunny woods, dark caves, soaring mountains, steaming jungles, vast oceans, and gloomy castles for the Super Happy Tree, which has been stolen by the dreaded Baby Bowser. Yoshi can walk, run, swim, leap, flutter, and fire his payload of eggs. The action takes place in storybook "pages" made up of bookmaking materials and other familiar textures, including cut-paper forests, denim clouds, inflatable plastic islands, and stacks of colored spools.

Yoshi's Story pioneers use of the Rumble Pak as a key element of the game-play experience, as you'll be able to feel invisible but treacherous currents when Yoshi swims through oceanic depths. The Rumble Pak can also help you locate hidden fruit or other objects by rumbling when Yoshi smells something. With a light touch of the Control Stick you can float on a leaf, ride a friendly dragon, and tiptoe past a swarm of angry bees.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Yoshi's Story (USA) (En,Ja).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Yoshi's Story (USA) (En,Ja).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Yoshi's Story (USA) (En,Ja).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19980310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Action-Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev A).n64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Kazooie</name>
		<desc>Banjo-Kazooie's fairy tale back story is reminiscent of Snow White's. A gnarled, ugly witch named Gruntilda asks her magical cauldron who is the fairest of them all. Of course, the pot's answer doesn't please the hag-- he singles out Banjo's sister, Tooty. When Tooty turns up missing, Banjo and his birdie buddy Kazooie set out to find her. 

The worlds in Banjo-Kazooie are gigantic, and chock full of crazy items to collect. Musical Notes, Puzzle Pieces ("Jiggies"), Mumbo Tokens, and Jinjoes are just some of the swag that Banjo must stuff in his backpack to complete his adventure. While some of the necessary items are simply stashed off the beaten path, others will require puzzle solving skills to turn up.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev A).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev A).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo - Rare</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Action / Adventure-Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Perfect Dark (USA) (Rev A).n64</path>
		<name>Perfect Dark</name>
		<desc>Joanna Dark is an agent for the Carrington Institute, a secret organization funded by anonymous sources and dedicated to protecting the world.  Through their highly trained operatives and special devices (gadgets), Carrington keeps an eye on terrorists, world powers, and strange happenings. The speed in which the dataDyne corporation has established itself through the development of new technologies is starting to worry the institute. So when Carrington receives a message from Dr. Caroll, a scientist wishing to escape dataDyne, they send their best agent, Joanna, to infiltrate the company headquarters...

Perfect Dark is a first person game similar to Rare's earlier Goldeneye: 007 though with more of an emphasis on stealth. Joanna can pick up and use a variety of firearms.  In addition she carries quite a few spy gadgets such as IR scanners, night vision, probes, and a deadly laptop.

The Xbox 360 port has redone graphics to support a 1080p full HD resolution at 60 frames per second. It also incorporates full multiplayer support over Xbox LIVE.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Perfect Dark (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Perfect Dark (USA) (Rev A).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Perfect Dark (USA) (Rev A).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action-Shooter / 1st person</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok - Dinosaur Hunter (USA) (Rev B).n64</path>
		<name>Turok : Dinosaur Hunter</name>
		<desc>Much like your usual 1st person shooter, although with dinosaurs as your main enemy. Includes 14 high tech weapons, like the Quad Rocket Launcher and the Atomic Fusion Cannon. You control Turok, who must take on the Campaigner and his highly evolved dino's. The objective is to collect pieces of the Chronoscepter, which is the only weapon that can help to destroy the Campaigner, and to stop him from using the power of the weapon to destroy the Lost Land.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Turok - Dinosaur Hunter (USA) (Rev B).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Turok - Dinosaur Hunter (USA) (Rev B).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Turok - Dinosaur Hunter (USA) (Rev B).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Shooter / 1st person</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Doom 64 (USA) (Rev A).n64</path>
		<name>Doom 64</name>
		<desc>DOOM 64 picks up where all the other DOOM games left off. After tearing through space, hell, and wherever else in the previous games, the  Space Marine thought that the threat of the demons was finally past. Of course, one survived, and it is currently reanimating all of the fallen monsters in a last-ditch attempt to revitalize their evil mission. The player's task is to finally rid the universe of all the crazy hellions, from the dead guy with the pistol to the rocket-spewing Cyberdemon.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Doom 64 (USA) (Rev A).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Doom 64 (USA) (Rev A).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Doom 64 (USA) (Rev A).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>id Software - Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em Up-Action-Shooter-Shooter / 1st person</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64</name>
		<desc>Mario is super in a whole new way! Combining the finest 3-D graphics ever developed for a video game and an explosive sound track, Super Mario 64 becomes a new standard for video games. It's packed with bruising battles, daunting obstacle courses and underwater adventures. Retrieve the Power Stars from their hidden locations and confront your arch nemesis - Bowser, King of the Koopas!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Super Mario 64 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Super Mario 64 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Super Mario 64 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart 64 (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
		<desc>Mario Kart 64 races eight familiar faces, including Mario, Bowser and Yoshi, on four progressively tougher four-track circuits. Wide curves and gentle banks mark the Mushroom Cup tracks. Your commute gets notably tougher on the Flower Cup, though. The player will have to dodge semis rumbling on Toad's Turnpike and bounding boulders on fogbound Choco Mountain! Star Cup tracks range from the icy surfaces of Sherbet Land to the lava lakes of Bowser's Castle. The true test of karting competence, though, comes on the four tracks in Special Cup. Zip through the dark caves and green hillsides of Donkey Kong's Jungle Parkway, cling to the sheer cliffs of Yoshi Valley and hustle over haunted Banshee Boardwalk before tackling the longest track in the game: neon-lit Rainbow Road. 

The game offers two camera angles and three engine sizes: 50cc, 100cc and 150cc. You can gain even more speed by mastering the power slide technique or grabbing Super Star power-ups. Each kart has distinctive handling, acceleration and top speed capabilities. Light karts like Princess's smoothly steer through tight corners, but run the constant risk of getting flattened by heavy karts, like Donkey Kong's. Shells that you fire at rival racers, Bananas that make them skid out and Lightning Bolts that make them small and very slow are just a few of the game's unique power-ups.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mario Kart 64 (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mario Kart 64 (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mario Kart 64 (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving-Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Mario Party</name>
		<desc>You know Mario can jump. You know he can kick Bowser's tail from here to the moon, but we bet you didn't realize that Mario is the biggest party animal on the face of the Earth. Nintendo is throwing the most insane bash to ever hit the N64, and you're invited. For the first time, you'll catch a glimpse of how Mario celebrates all of the victories he's had over the years. 

Mario Party is unlike any other game for the N64, and it just might be the best party game to ever hit the system. Mario Party is designed for 1 to 4 players, but it's not really a party unless you're playing with your pals. The festivities are based on a board game format, right down to the fact that players must roll a die to determine how many spaces to move. The fun starts when players land on different squares, because each space holds one of more than fifty different mini-games. These quick competitions determine who will earn coins and stars, and who will go home empty handed. 

 The mini-games are spread over eight different game boards, all of which are not immediately available. Some of the games pit every man or princess against the others, some are two-on-two, and others are even three against one. The games are simple, but remarkably fun to play. One challenge is loosely based on "Simon Says," another involves a two-on-two bobsled race, and one crazy game makes one player attempt to cross a rope while the other three do their best to shake the player off. You'll find skill games, racing games, puzzle games --basically any type of challenge you could imagine. 

A good portion of the actual game boards are animated, with hidden dangers and special challenges scattered everywhere. Mario, Luigi, Princess Peach, Donkey Kong, Bowser, Yoshi, and Wario are all invited to the party, and each character has his or her own game board. 

Mario Party is fun for only one player, but to get the most out of this party-in-a-pak, you should play with three other friends. It's definitely the kind of game that will keep you up till the wee hours of the morning, so you might want to start catching up on your sleep right away.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Mario Party (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Mario Party (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Mario Party (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo - Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA) (Rev B).n64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda : Ocarina of Time</name>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule. He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce. As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf's evil schemes. Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora's Domain. Before you complete this epic quest, you'll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA) (Rev B).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA) (Rev B).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA) (Rev B).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19981123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role playing games-Action / Adventure</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1080 Snowboarding (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).n64</path>
		<name>1080 Snowboarding</name>
		<image>./mixart/1080 Snowboarding (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).png</image>
		<video>./snap/1080 Snowboarding (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/1080 Snowboarding (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).png</marquee>
		<releasedate />
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre />
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AeroGauge (USA).n64</path>
		<name>AeroGauge</name>
		<desc>Blaze through the skies as you take control of your very own Aeromachines in this new futuristic racing game, AeroGauge. With courses that have sharp turns, and even sharper obstacles, it is going to take a keen eye and ultimate control to maneuver through courses featuring canyons, tunnels, oceans, and mountains. Imagine speeds reaching over 1000 mph as you whiz by the field in route to victory in these graphically advanced landscapes. Never has a game incorporated such remarkable control, detailed graphics, and mind-tingling speeds as AeroGauge!</desc>
		<image>./mixart/AeroGauge (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/AeroGauge (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/AeroGauge (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19980430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Locomotive Games</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Entertainment Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Automobili Lamborghini (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Automobili Lamborghini</name>
		<desc>Automobili Lamborghini is one of the earlier racing games for the Nintendo 64, developed by Titus. 8 cars are included in this game, among them the Lamborghini Diablo, Porsche 959, Ferrari F50 and some hidden ones. The courses are quite detailed and the effects are decent, including special effects like lens flares. Races take you through six circuits in exotic areas around the world. There are 4 modes in Single Player including Arcade Mode, Championship Mode, Single Race and Time Trials. The game also includes 4 player support.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Automobili Lamborghini (USA).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Automobili Lamborghini (USA).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Automobili Lamborghini (USA).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19971130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Titus</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F1 Pole Position 64 (USA) (En,Fr,De).n64</path>
		<name>F1 Pole Position 64</name>
		<desc>A Formula 1 racing game, officially acknowledged by the FIA F1 World Championship, containing the 16 World championship circuits of the day, ranging from Monza and the old Hockenheim to Monaco and the Hungaroring. 

Car setup is highly detailed, reflecting real Formula One and the game's simulation basis. You will have to race in the wet, which means further setup modification to cope with the reduced grip. You can also edit the level of car damage, the pit-car radio, and whether the CPU cars can collide. There are also Battle and Time Trial modes, with your best laptimes recorded.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/F1 Pole Position 64 (USA) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
		<video>./snap/F1 Pole Position 64 (USA) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/F1 Pole Position 64 (USA) (En,Fr,De).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Human - Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Various-Race, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania (USA) (Rev B).n64</path>
		<name>Castlevania</name>
		<desc>Konami's long-running series of Castlevania games makes its debut on the N64. The traditional 2D graphics have been left behind; this is the first Castlevania game in 3D. However, the goal of the game remains the same: kick some vampire butt as you battle the evil Count Dracula and his minions in this platformer.

The player can either choose to be Reinhardt Schneider (for the traditional whip action) or Carrie Fernandez (who uses magical powers). Both characters have their own story line. A nice feature is the presence of an in-game clock which changes the time of the day (either day or night).

Reinhardt &amp; Carrie both appear again in the second Castlevania game for the N64: Castlevania: Legacy of Darkness, which has new layouts for the levels of this game.</desc>
		<image>./mixart/Castlevania (USA) (Rev B).png</image>
		<video>./snap/Castlevania (USA) (Rev B).mp4</video>
		<marquee>./wheel/Castlevania (USA) (Rev B).png</marquee>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure-Action-Action / Adventure-Platform</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>